Say, look who got out tonight.
She kicked it out. She let me out. She
loves me. Now wait till she knows you,
Doris. She's part of my future.
Know what I see in your future?
What?
A great big house with a great big
mortgage.
Wait, three kids,
all going to college at the same time.
What a tradition.
What a tuition.
Ooh, and retirement on a sunny little
island. All right, you guys. Can you see
how I'm going to handle all that
with perseverance
and a piece of the rock?
A piece of the rock. Credential
insurance. Highly recommended. In fact,
in a national survey, when asked which
life insurance company they'd recommend,
more people recommended Credential than
any other insurance company.
Hey, I see something in here for you.
What?
A hole for your thumb.
For Life, Health, Auto, Home. Get a
piece of the rock.
Credential insurance.